[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
[MEN GRUNT]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OMENG] Move the Knight.
- [TOMAS] Don't teach him!
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RATS SQUEAKING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[TATANG] Gabo.
Looks like the Crusaders
are planning to escape.
If that happens,
it's going to be a big mess.
Be careful.
[TOMAS] Tatang, Omeng.
They're going to start a riot
to create a distraction.
They'll escape,
that's their plan.
[TOMAS] Let's go with them.
We'll just rot in here
otherwise.
We're never getting out
of this place.
We'll just die here.
Those people?
They'll just sell you out.
They'll use us as bait
for the police.
What do you think, Gabo?
We're not escaping.
We're not joining them either.
I'll serve my sentence here.
I'll prove to them that
I didn't do anything wrong,
that I was falsely accused.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I respect your principles.
You're willing to stay here
and endure all this
just to prove your innocence.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- The Knight!
- Don't teach him!
[TOMAS] Just let him play.
[OMINOUS MUSIC SWELLS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[MAN YELLING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[MAN Hey!
- Hey!
- [OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[KNIFE SWINGS]
[FLESH RIPS]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [OMENG] Gabo!
Tatang's been stabbed!
- [OMENG] Tomas!
- Get Tatang out of here!
- Help!
- Hurry!
[BLOWS LANDING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[BLOW LANDS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[GUNSHOTS]
You! Get down!
Troublemaker!
Get down!
You again, Gabo?
You started this again,
didn't you?
You never learn!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GABO GRUNTS]
Take him!
Bring him to the solitary cell!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[GABO] Let me go!
I shouldn't be here.
You bastards!
Let me out!
I didn't do anything wrong.
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
I swear...
when I get out of here, Django,
I will make you pay
for all the suffering
I experienced here.
I will kill you.
I'm going to kill you.
This is less than usual.
Are you skimming off my share.
Django, would we even
do that to you?
The target is too big
for us to take on.
It's hard to refuse.
- The payout's huge.
- So who's going to do it?
Who else?
Django.
Just make sure of it.
Because if I find out
you're stealing from me,
I'll cut off your heads.
He needs to lead the group
starting now.
- [DJANGO] Alright.
- You're right.
Django!
We've got a job tomorrow.
The target's a congressman.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
What exactly is the job?
We're killing him.
Isn't that dangerous, Pa?
bring someone with guts.
Who?
That one.
Gabo.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
But Django...
if things go south,
just leave him behind.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Your father's right, Django.
It's time for you
to take over the group.
[DJANGO]
We've got a job tomorrow.
- Target's a congressman.
- A congressman?
That guy's got bodyguards.
He might fight back.
Are you scared?
You're such a weakling.
Gabo, you're coming
with me tomorrow.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Django...
[BOTTLE THUDS]
That guy's a big shot.
It won't be an easy job.
Our lives will surely
be at stake.
Are you scared?
- Here.
- [GUN CLATTERS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're not going to kill him.
We're just going to scare him.
You're just going
to rough him up.
Don't worry, Gabo.
We've got strong connections.
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
- [MOTORCYCLE ENGINES REVVING]
- [CAR ENGINES REVVING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [CAR HORN HONKS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MAN] Run him over!
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[LOUD CRASH]
[GUNSHOTS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BODY THUD]
Why did you shoot him?!
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[HELMET THUD]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TABLE CLATTERS]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [WATER SPLASHING]
[BOXES CLATTERING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Django!
[BLOWS LANDING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[KICK LANDS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[BOX CLATTERS]
[BLOW LANDS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[MOTORCYCLE ROARING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KICK LANDS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [BOXES CLATTERING]
- [BOTTLES SHATTERING]
[BRAKE SCREECH]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[LOUD THUD]
- [EXPLOSION]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Django!
You bastard!
That wasn't part of our deal!
Why did you shoot him?!
You betrayed me!
You bastard!
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GUN THUDS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GRUNTING]
[KICKS LANDING]
[GRUNTING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
[THUD]
[KICKS LAND]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [BLOWS, KICKS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[LOUD CRASH]
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
Get up!
[BLOWS LAND]
[BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[KICK LANDS]
You bastard!
[GABO PANTING]
I'll never forget
what you did to me.
[PANTING]
I'm leaving your group.
[BLOWS LANDING]
If I see you here again...
I will kill you!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTS]
[GABO HUFFS]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[SIRENS CONTINUE WAILING]
Nobody make a move!
[COP] Hands up!
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN CLATTERS]
[RAT SQUEAKING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[METAL GATE RATTLES]
- Stand up!
- What do you want from me?!
What are you
going to do to me?!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OFFICER] Now what?!
[GABO] What are you
going to do to me?!
Let me go!
- Walk! Just walk!
- [RAT SQUEAKING]
[GABO] What are you
going to do?!
Let me go! [GRUNTS]
You're stubborn, huh!
- [BODY THUD]
- [GABO GROANS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you
going to do to me?!
Come on.
- Stand up!
- [GRUNTS]
- Let me go!
Come here! [GROANS]
I heard you're tough.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GABO GRUNTING]
Fix yourself!
- [GABO EXHALES]
- Go!
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- [GURGLING]
- Don't stop!
- Aah!
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- [GABO GURGLING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GABO PANTS]
- What?
- One more!
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- [GABO GURGLING]
[GABO PANTING]
What?!
- Oh, okay!
- Go!
[THUD]
[GRUNTING]
You're tough, huh!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ROPE CREAKS]
- [GABO GRUNTS, GROANS]
[BASIN SLIDES]
[RAT SQUEAKS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [WATER SPLASHES]
[GROANING]
Don't fight back!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Speak up!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[GROANS]
Whatever you do...
...you can't make me bend!
You're tough.
He's really tough.
[ELECTRIC SPARKS]
Let's see how tough you are.
- Mm-hmm. Let's see.
- [ELECTRIC SPARKING]
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
[ELECTRIC SPARKING]
- [SCREAMING]
- [BUZZING]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
- [SCREAMING]
- [BUZZING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[BUZZING]
[SCREAMING]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
[GROANING]
[ELECTRIC BUZZING]
[GABO'S SCREAMS ECHOING]
- Herode.
- Sir.
[GABO GROANING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's see how tough you are!
[SCREAMING]
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- [ROPE TWISTING]
- [THWACKS]
- [GABO GRUNTS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GUARDS GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[KICKS LANDING]
- [WOOD CLATTERS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [WATER SPLASHES]
- [THUD]
- [GRUNTS]
- [KICKS, BLOWS LANDING]
- [GUARDS GRUNTING]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[KICKS LANDING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[BLOW, KICKS LAND]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[KEYS JANGLING]
- Get him in there.
- Hey, get up! Wake up!
Wake up.
Oh, no!
I got him.
[GABO GRUNTING WEAKLY]
Ow!
[MACARAIG] Hey! Listen up!
Anyone who stirs up trouble
will answer to me.
Hey, Grandpa!
Tell him to behave
if he still wants to live!
[OMENG] Go back to sleep!
Go!
Drop the brave act, Gabo.
You won't win
against them.
What you should do
is get out of here.
Before they kill you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Gabo, you should
break out tonight.
Gabo.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Gabo, this is the key.
When everyone is asleep
head for the exit
and escape.
You won't make it
to sunrise if you don't.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
[LOCK CLINKING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS FAINTLY]
[TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [SIREN BLARING]
- Gabo!
Where are you going?
[SIREN BLARING]
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [FLESH SQUELCHING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[BODY THUDS]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIREN BLARING DISTANTLY]
I'm not breaking out.
I'm going to fight...
for the truth.
[DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN]
Gabo.
Have a seat.
Why did you call me in?
Good news.
We'll have one less
troublemaker in here.
You're free to go.
[FOLDER SHUFFLES]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
We're just waiting
for your release order.
Everyone! Gabo is free!
[PRISONERS TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
- Gabo's a free man!
- Take care outside, man.
Be nice in here.
Sure thing!
- Take care, man.
- Hey!
Don't forget about us
when you're out.
I'll be going now.
- Take care.
- Bye, Gabo!
Mister Omeng, Mister Tomas.
I'll be going now.
Take care.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Oh! Uh, Gabo, wait.
Take this. It's some savings
from the group.
- Take it.
- No, I'm good.
Come on.
It'll help you start again.
- It's okay.
- Thank you.
Gabo, can you also
check on my parole?
Come on now!
What does he know about that?
Well, he doesn't know
about his parole, either.
- Who knows?
- Oh, you.
[OMENG]
Just let the kid go out.
I know, I know, but...
Tatang...
I'm going out today.
Oh, it must be nice to be out.
Don't worry, Tatang.
I'm sure
you'll get your day, too.
I'll meet you outside, by then.
I think I'm gonna die in here
because of my sentence.
Tatang, don't say that.
You'll get out too.
I hope, Gabo,
you don't waste this opportunity
in your life.
Do your best to not
come back here.
Don't worry.
I promise.
I'm never going back here.
I hope, in your new journey,
you will use your fiery heart
for the good.
I'll keep that in mind,
Tatang.
Mister Omeng, Mister Tomas.
[OMENG] Take care, Gabo.
- Hey, Gabo!
- Hey, it's Gabo!
Gabo is going out!
Gabo, take care!
Take care outside, Gabo!
Take care in here.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
[HOPEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GATE SQUEAKS CLOSE]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUS CONDUCTOR] Alright, now.
For those who haven't paid up,
bring it in.
Who doesn't have a ticket yet?
- [VENDOR] Peanuts here!
- Come on.
[BUS CONDUCTOR] Wait up!
Come on in!
Who doesn't have ticket yet?
Come on, pay up.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Your fare, please.
- Where are you headed?
- Ginintuang Lupa.
Ginintuang Lupa.
[COINS JINGLE]
Who else doesn't have a ticket?
How about you?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GABO] Now that I'm free,
I promise myself.
I'm going to change my ways
and give my life
some direction.
I'm not going to let us
be poor forever,
suffering for eternity.
I will do anything
to get my life in order.
I will help my family
and my neighbors.
[YOUNG GABO] How long
are we going to stay here?
[YOUNG RUDY]
Do you miss our old house?
I miss Mommy.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Son...
We're not going back
to our old life.
We can't be with Mommy anymore.
But don't worry.
We won't be
at rock bottom forever.
The earth is round, son.
Our fate will change eventually.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Come here. I'm going
to give you something.
This coin gave me luck.
It changed my life.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
That will give you luck, too.
[GABO] I will not waste
this opportunity.
This time, I'll change
my family's destiny.
We won't be...
at rock bottom forever.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [HORNS HONKING]
- [SIRENS WAILING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I hope today turns out well.
I'm wearing your watch,
after all.
I miss you, RJ.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAX] Good morning, sis!
- Good morning, Max.
- Come here.
Mmm, my baby girl.
Hm?
[MAX SIGHS]
Is everything okay?
Thinking about RJ again?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Not a day goes by
that I don't think about him.
We all miss him.
Please stop blaming yourself
for what happened.
It wasn't your fault, okay?
If you ever need someone
to talk to,
I'm here.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] I know.
How's Dad?
Dad?
He's in a good mood today.
Don't worry about him.
I know things will
get better soon.
So cheer up. Hmm? Hmm?
If you need anything,
I'm just here.
I just need to grab something
from my room.
I'll see you downstairs. Okay?
- See you.
- Mwah!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[RICARDO] I'm telling you,
solar power is
a great investment,
especially now that electricity
prices keep going up.
Since we've been saving money
on electricity,
I think it's about time
we buy an electric car.
Gas is so expensive these days.
Oh, ma'am!
A new car would suit you
perfectly
because you're so fresh.
- [LAUGHS]
- What about me?
Of course, sir.
You're also fresh!
[LAUGHING]
Good morning, Mom, Dad.
Oh!
My beautiful daughter.
Mm. [CHUCKLES]
Twinkle, can I have
some coffee, please?
[TWINKLE] Oh, right.
I'll do it. Thank you.
- [RICARDO] Twinkle!
- Sir?
I'll just have water.
Thank you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh...
Come on, join us for breakfast.
[MAX] I'm late! I'm late!
I'm late! I'm late!
- Oh.
- [MAX] I got to go.
- I'm running late.
- Oh.
- Dad, I got to go.
- Oh, wait.
- Why?
- Hon, you have to hear this.
Did you know Captain Umali,
her coworker, called me
and commended her
for their buy-bust operation!
Well done, dear.
Good job.
Max, remember...
I have high expectations
for you.
Remember, you're
carrying the surname Jacinto.
Copy, sir.
Carry on.
I got to go. Sis.
Bye.
Oh, how about you, Sam?
How's work at the NCIA?
We're doing alright.
We've just arrested
the Zaragoza syndicate.
They're the ones behind
the bank heists in Manila.
[ISOBEL] Wow!
I heard about that.
And that's very good.
That's one less group
of criminals out there.
Right, hon?
As it should be. Good.
[ISOBEL SIGHS]
- I'd better get going too.
- Wait, you haven't eaten yet.
Oh, it's alright.
- [ISOBEL] Wait. Twinkle!
- [TWINKLE] Yes, ma'am?
- Pack some food for her.
- Okay, ma'am.
[TOTO] Oh, ma'am!
Got her running like a dream!
- Thank you.
- [TOTO CHUCKLES]
[TWINKLE] Ma'am!
Ma'am, Madam Isabel
said you should bring this.
Thank you.
Hey, Sam, eat healthy, okay?
And, um...
And try to be patient
with your dad.
I understand where
Dad's coming from.
Take care. I love you.
Mm.
I love you.
Okay.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[ISOBEL] Bye.
Bye!
[ENGINE STARTING]
Hey.
Where's my food?
[TOTO] Give me some food too.
[TWINKLE] Dream on!
She's making my heart flutter!
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [PASSENGERS SCREAMING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[PASSENGERS SCREAM]
Hey, Mister!
You're driving too fast!
You're going to kill us
at this rate!
Just hold on tight!
I'm sorry, but we're in a hurry.
We need to pick up
more passengers.
You know how high
gas prices are.
We need to earn money.
[HORN HONKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [PASSENGERS SCREAMING]
[CLAMORING]
My goodness, I'm getting off!
You drive so recklessly!
We're all going to die
at this rate!
My goodness!
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Keep walking.
There are vacant seats
at the back.
[BUS CONDUCTOR]
There are some seats left.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BUS CONDUCTOR]
Your fare, please.
Where are you getting off,
mister?
Tondo.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[PASSENGER] Jeez, mister.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Seriously, Noel?!
What happened to it?
I don't know what's wrong
with it, madam.
You never know anything!
Hey!
The car I told you to book,
where is it?
The phone ran out of juice.
Where's the power bank?
Oh no.
I forgot to bring it, madam.
[GROWLS]
So, what do we do now?
I have an important meeting!
- [HORN HONKING]
- [VEHICLE APPROACHING]
Oh, madam, why don't
we just take the bus?
What?!
We have no choice!
- [HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[PASSENGERS EXCLAIM]
- Let's go, please.
- Fine!
Come on, madam,
let's hop on.
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
Noel is unbelievable.
Just when I'm in a rush
for a meeting,
that's when the car
breaks down.
Because he never checks it!
And you, you're irritating too!
- Madam--
- Don't you know?
The client is about to pay
the down payment
for the condo!
If I don't make it, you're both
going to be in trouble!
Hold on, hold on.
I want to sit there.
Make her leave.
Miss, maybe you could sit
at the back.
[WOMAN] Why? I was here first!
- She should sit there!
- Miss?
It's okay. There's still a
vacant sit here. Come on.
- Please, miss.
- Oh, seriously?!
What a pain!
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Put some alcohol on it!
[BOTTLE SPRAYING]
Hurry! Come on, faster!
Such a slowpoke!
- Now, sit there! Come on!
- Yes, ma'am.
Looks like we'll make a
killing with her.
She seems loaded.
[HORN HONKING]
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Fan me! I'm feeling hot!
Alright, everyone.
This is a holdup!
[PASSENGERS SCREAMING IN FEAR]
Give me your bag! Now!
- Do it!
- Keep driving!
- [OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Just keep driving!
[ENGINE ROARING]
- [WINDOW SHATTERS]
- [HORN HONKING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Hand over your bag!
- [WOMAN] Please, no!
Talk about bad luck, huh?
- [BONES CRACK]
- [WHIMPERS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
Don't stop!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GEAR STICK CLICKS]
[HORNS HONKING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
[WINDOW SHATTERS]
Gabo!
So, you're out now.
Who would've thought
we'd meet here?
Damn you, Boy Topak!
Your crew with Django
is ruthless.
You'll even go after cold rice.
Life is so hard these days,
I'd even eat burnt rice.
- [LOUD THWACK]
- [CRIES]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
[KICK LANDS]
- [HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE ROARING]
[HORN HONKING]
[KNIFE WHOOSHING]
[KICK LANDS]
[BLOW LANDS]
[LOUD THWACK]
[WINDOW SHATTERS]
[BODY THUDDING]
- [HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE ROARING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [LOUD THUD]
- [HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE ROARING]
[HORN HONKING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [LOUD THUD]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[LINE RINGING]
- Hello, Max? Where are you?
- Sam.
I need backup on Joaquin Street!
There's a holdup happening
on a bus!
- We're on our way there.
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- [ENGINE ROARING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KICK LANDS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[HEAVY THUD]
[KICK LANDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is the police! Stop!
Stop the bus!
[GUNSHOTS]
[KNIFE WHOOSHING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [LOUD THWACK]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BODY THUDS]
[KNIFE WHOOSHES]
[BLOW LANDS]
[GUNFIRE]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOT]
- [BLOW, KICK LANDING]
- [PASSENGERS SCREAMING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
You're tough, Gabo, huh?
[BLOWS LANDING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BODY THUDS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[KICK LANDS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[BODY THUDDING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
[LOUD THUD]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[CAR ENGINE STOPS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Get off!
I said get off!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] Thank you!
I told you to stop the bus!
Hey!
I'm not the robber!
I'm the one who helped them!
Don't lie.
I saw you.
[SCOFFS]
I saved your life.
And now you're pointing
a gun at me?
Don't move.
Fire that gun if you want.
I don't care.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey! I told you not to move!
One!
Gabo!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GROANS] Agh!
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA"
BY ARIEL RIVERA PLAYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Let's go!
[WOMAN]
He's not-- He's not the robber!
He's not the robber!
He helped us!
Poor thing! Help him!
Please help him!
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
He's not the robber!
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA" CONTINUES]
- [RECORD SCRATCH SFX]
- [SLAPS]
You're crazy!
- Ouch! Agh!
- You pervert!
You sicko!
- [GABO GROANS]
- Get up!
Agh!
You pervert!
You took advantage of me!
Took advantage?
You're the one who kissed me!
You took advantage of me!
Oh, you really had the nerve!
I was only trying to help!
[SCOFFS]
Miss, you are the one
I have helped!
I just saved your life!
Between us, I'm the one
who should sue.
Hey, what you did to me
was child abuse!
- What?
- Oh--
I mean, sexual abuse. Right?
You really had the nerve!
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
Miss, don't you know who I am?
If I sue you,
you'll be in jail for sure!
You really had the nerve,
don't you?
[VIA] Clear the perimeter!
You're beautiful.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VIA] Ryan!
- What's your name?
You're unbelievable.
You had the guts
to ask my name.
Sam!
Look, I'm leaving.
Take care of the robbers.
- Sam! Sam!
- Hey!
- Hold on! We're not done!
- Are you alright?
[SAM] Yes. I'm fine.
You guys look cute.
How fortunate.
You truly are my lucky charm.
[SMACK]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA"
BY ARIEL RIVERA PLAYING]
"This Tuesday."
Why did he kiss you?
He kissed Ma'am Sam
before you could.
I said enough.
He did me wrong.
I'll make him pay myself.
If I find out who he is,
I'll arrest him, not you.
I'm back where I belong.
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Gabo! Gabo!
- Django should know this.
- He won't last here long.
He's dead meat.
I'll make sure he dies
here in Ginintuang Lupa.
Gabo, if you're really brave,
face Django.
He turned a new leaf.
I'll bet you guys.
He'll turn his life around.
- Fine.
- Call.
You bastards!
Django!